# Atharva Bhawsar

# **Frontend Developer**

## Skills

HTML5 CSS

**JavaScript** 

Java

ReactJS

Gatsby

AdobeXD

Figma

UI design

**UX** engineering

Git

GitHub

#### **Socials**

Twitter
LinkedIn
GitHub
Hashnode

Hobbies

Football Sketching Cars Documentaries Video Games

## **Profile**

My name is Atharva and I am a pre-final year student pursuing a bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Engineering. I have a strong passion for all things related to technology and strive to become a well-rounded generalist in the field. I am more focused on developer technologies and have experience in web engineering and DevOps.

Besides development, I am also a Technical content creator on Twitter and enjoy engaging and sharing resources and ideas while making valuable connections.

#### **Education**

B.tech, Guru Ghasidas University (2020 - 2024)

Bilaspur

Student of Computer Science and Engineering. GPA: 8.56 (Current)

### Work Experience

#### Web Designer, Udaan

(April 2022 - Present)

Implemented UI and UX of the official website of Udaan. Assisted with full-stack web development using React and Django.

Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, AdobeXD

#### Web Developer, MedicsCode

(Jun 2021 - October 2021)

Designed and Developed websites for medical professionals. Using HTML5, CSS, Javascript, and PHP, I developed interactive websites with user-friendly functionalities such as contact forms, services section, etc.

Skills: Web Design with CMS.

## **Key Projects**

**To-Do List** React + Vite

Users can add tasks to a list, mark tasks as complete, and remove tasks from the list. Additionally, the application features accent color changing and light and dark mode functionalities for a more customizable experience.

Source Link

Mapty JavaScript

This is a simple workout tracker made using the LeafLet maps API. This enables the user with tracking their workouts using their locations.

**Source Link** 

Tesla Clone React + Redux

Tesla Website with React. I have used Styled Components in this for Styling and also used Material UI for icons. Added some animations using transitions and keyframes

**Source Link**